everythingusb.com 2001-06-02

# USB Workshop

## Privacy Statement

Cosmo Communications Co. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: USB Workshop.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **USB Workshop** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

(*Since you indicated that there are special relationships, such as "Powered by" partners, business partners, cobranded sites, then these relationships must be addressed in your privacy statement. These relationships need to be clearly defined and it must be clear who is receiving the information collected by the site and who has access to this information. It must be clear what type of information is shared. Is only select information shared? Is the sharing of information limited to only aggregate information?)

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. (*Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place.)

## Children's Guidelines

According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program.

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  1. You can send email to [editors@usbworkshop.com](mailto:editors@usbworkshop.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact  
Ian Chiu Cosmo Communications Co. 5560 McColl Crescent [editors@usbworkshop.com](mailto:editors@usbworkshop.com)
